<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on stefanwalther.io</title>
    <link>https://stefanwalther.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on stefanwalther.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://stefanwalther.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Docker Images - Check the Size</title>
      <link>https://stefanwalther.io/blog/docker-image-size/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stefanwalther.io/blog/docker-image-size/</guid>
      <description>When building Docker Images one can easily forget to optimize the size of the images. Therefore I prefer to always get the immediate feedback, how large the resulting docker images is.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a small, reusable script, I use in some of my projects, a reusable section in a Makefile.
DOCKER_IMAGE_NAME = &amp;lt;your-docker-image-name&amp;gt; DOCKER_IMAGE_SIZE = $(shell docker images --format &amp;quot;{{.Repository}} {{.Size}}&amp;quot; | grep $(DOCKER_IMAGE_NAME) | cut -d\ -f2) build: ## Build the docker image docker build -t $(DOCKER_IMAGE_NAME) .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - the Next Bad Guy?</title>
      <link>https://stefanwalther.io/blog/github-bad-guy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stefanwalther.io/blog/github-bad-guy/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s not that long ago, that Microsoft was the bad guy for everything happening in the IT-industry. It was just cool to bash MS in favor of any Linux/Open-Source solution.
Now we have 2017, the situation has changed dramatically:
 Microsoft is starting to become cool, being the Nr. 1 contributor in the Open Source world Microsoft and Google have swapped places: &amp;ldquo;Microsoft is The New Google, Google is the Old Microsoft&amp;ldquo; GitHub has become one of the major dependencies for every IT-company  I claim that GitHub has a huge potential to become the new bad guy in the industry:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yet another blog. Why?</title>
      <link>https://stefanwalther.io/blog/yet-another-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stefanwalther.io/blog/yet-another-blog/</guid>
      <description>I like to blog. I like to share.
In the recent years I have primarily created content on qlikblog.at, then I shared quite some solutions &amp;amp; prototypes on GitHub and recently I have started a new blog called qliksite.io
So why creating another blog?
While all the efforts in the past primarily focused on projects, prototypes to spread the word in the Qlik ecosystem (QlikView, Qlik Sense &amp;amp; Qlik Analytics Plaform), there is just more I want to write about:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>