<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on stefanwalther.io</title>
    <link>http://stefanwalther.io/blog/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on stefanwalther.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://stefanwalther.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Yet another blog. Why?</title>
      <link>http://stefanwalther.io/blog/2017/04/yet-another-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stefanwalther.io/blog/2017/04/yet-another-blog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I like to blog. I like to share.&lt;br /&gt;
In the recent years I have primarily created content on &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.qlikblog.at&#34;&gt;qlikblog.at&lt;/a&gt;, then I shared quite some solutions &amp;amp; prototypes &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/stefanwalther&#34;&gt;on GitHub&lt;/a&gt; and recently I have started a new blog called &lt;a href=&#34;http://qliksite.io&#34;&gt;qliksite.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So why creating another blog?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While all the efforts in the past primarily focused on projects, prototypes to spread the word in the Qlik ecosystem (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.qlik.com/us/products/qlikview&#34;&gt;QlikView&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.qlik.com/us/products/qlik-sense&#34;&gt;Qlik Sense&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.qlik.com/us/products/qlik-analytics-platform&#34;&gt;Qlik Analytics Plaform&lt;/a&gt;), there is just more I want to write about:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General trends in the IT-space, Cloud Computing, IoT, microservices, Docker, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General programming topics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am a big fan and adopter of IoT, having build a pretty crazy environment at home, which I&amp;rsquo;d like to start sharing &amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I have three boys, two of them are entering an age, where I can start building fun stuff together with them (Raspberry PI, robots, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learning new technologies is the spice of my professional life, it inspires me and helps me to innovate in my professional life, but it&amp;rsquo;s also just the enjoyable and free time I need on a daily basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So this blog is just a private one, just a place to share some ideas &amp;amp; thoughts - without really taking care what the professional periphery will think about it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>